<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<pmxi_records><job><job_reference>96467651</job_reference><position><![CDATA[Software Engineer (SCM)]]></position><description><![CDATA[At Northrop Grumman we develop cutting-edge technology that preserves freedom and advances human discovery. Our pioneering and inventive spirit has enabled us to be at the forefront of many technological advancements in our nation's history - from the first flight across the Atlantic Ocean, to stealth bombers, to landing on the moon. We continue to innovate with developments from launching the first commercial flight to space, to discovering the early beginnings of the universe. Our employees are not only part of history, they're making history.<br /> <br /> Northrop Grumman Aerospace Systems sector is seeking a Software Configuration Management Build Engineer – Band 2 to join our diverse team.<br /> <br /> The successful candidate's primary work will be as a member of the Software Configuration Management Build Team supporting multiple programs on a variety of different development platforms, primarily formal software and data product development efforts for processing and analyzing data from space sensors. The candidate will support the planning, execution, and maintenance of configuration-controlled operational-level software builds. As required by program needs, the candidate will be responsible for supporting multiple development teams in a dynamic, multi-platform environment.<br /> <br /> Responsibilities will include providing ClearCase/Git/Subversion and other version control tools administrative support including installations, user account management, Git repository, creation of VOBs & Views, and technical troubleshooting; providing software build support including makefile creation, build labeling, software builds and content list generation. Additional responsibilities may include developing and supporting scripts including triggers and integration with other products.<br /> <br /> For a candidate to be successful in this role they will need excellent written and oral communication skills. They will also require strong soft-skills and be comfortable with inter- and intra-team interactions.<br /> <br /> Basic Qualifications:<br /> <br /> * Candidate must have a Bachelor's Degree in a S.T.E.M. (Science, Technology, Engineering or Mathematics) Field<br /> <br /> * Minimum of 2 years in SCM and Software Build in Unix/Linux/Windows environment.<br /> <br /> * Ability to obtain and Maintain a DoD Secret Level Security Clearance. U.S. Citizenship is required.<br /> <br /> Preferred Qualifications:<br /> <br /> * Git, GitHub, Rational ClearCase, Subversion and other Version Control tools experience.<br /> <br /> * Atlassian JIRA, Rational ClearQuest and other Defect Tracking tools experience.<br /> <br /> * Atlassian Confluence and Bitbucket<br /> <br /> * Programming or scripting experience in an UNIX environment (C , Perl, Shell scripts). Experience with makefiles (ClearMake, GNUmake).<br /> <br /> * Knowledge of Military & Civil Space (SBIRS, JPSS, JTAGS P3I, iSAGE) program experience is a plus.<br /> <br /> * Experience in developing software configuration approaches and maintenance of the SCM library and processes.<br /> <br /> * Knowledge of languages C, C , Ada, Java, and Fortran and its compiler principle.<br /> <br /> Northrop Grumman is committed to hiring and retaining a diverse workforce. We are proud to be an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer, making decisions without regard to race, color, religion, creed, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, national origin, age, veteran status, disability, or any other protected class. For our complete EEO/AA and Pay Transparency statement, please visit www.northropgrumman.com/EEO. U.S. Citizenship is required for most positions.<p style='display: none; font-weight: bold;' hidden='hidden'>AC2019</p>]]></description><company><![CDATA[Northrop Grumman]]></company><postal_code>91702</postal_code><city>Azusa</city><state>CA</state><country>USA</country><url>https://www.startwire.com/jobs/azusa-ca/software-engineer-96467651?source=appconnect-ua</url><posted_date>2019/01/22</posted_date><category>Technology</category><ats>tee</ats><rpu_tag>medium</rpu_tag><employment_type>OTHER</employment_type><normalized_company>northrop-grumman</normalized_company><normalized_position>software engineer</normalized_position></job><job><job_reference>543439114</job_reference><position><![CDATA[Software Engineer]]></position><description><![CDATA[Are you interested in expanding your career through experience and exposure, all while supporting a mission that seeks to ensure the security of our nation and its allies? If so, then Northrop Grumman is the place for you. As a leading global security company, we provide innovative systems, products and solutions to our customers worldwide. We are comprised of diverse professionals that bring different perspectives and ideas, understanding that the more experiences we bring to our work the more innovative we can be. As we continue to build our workforce we look for people that exemplify our core values, leadership characteristics, and approach to innovation.<br /> <br /> Northrop Grumman Engineering, Systems, and Integration (ESI) business unit is a seeking a creative, skilled and motivated Software Systems Engineer to join our team at Vandenberg AFB, CA. This position offers an opportunity for the right candidate to perform systems engineering tasks for ICBM software applications for strategic defense systems, focusing on simulators used to support and train ICBM operations and maintenance performing the Nuclear Deterrence mission for the USAF.<br /> <br /> The successful candidate is anticipated to perform the following duties and responsibilities:<br /> <br /> * Technical planning, system software development, and integration<br /> <br /> * Utilize knowledge of software engineering policies and procedures<br /> <br /> * Technical analyses of concept, design, test and operation to ensure the logical and systematic conversion of customer or product requirements into systems software solutions that integrate/control weapon system simulation hardware components<br /> <br /> * Analyze operational systems and design hardware & software simulation solutions, author requirements, perform system integration and compatibility with legacy VAX/VMS environments to meet demanding, customer-driven fidelity requirements<br /> <br /> * Utilize good interpersonal communication skills to work in a team environment<br /> <br /> * Take on complex and challenging tasks with minimal direction and remain current on emerging technologies trends and insights<br /> <br /> * Interface with the customer, contractors, and other stake holders describing the software designs and solutions to trainer issues<br /> <br /> This requisition may be filled at a higher grade based on qualifications listed below.<br /> <br /> Basic Qualifications:<br /> <br /> * This requisition may be filled at either a level 2 or level 3<br /> <br /> * US Citizenship and the ability to obtain a DOD Top Secret Clearance<br /> <br /> * Bachelor's Degree in Electrical/Computer Engineering, Computer Science or other technically related field<br /> <br /> * Minimum 2 years of related experience with a Bachelor's degree; 0 years with a Master's degree (Level 3 requires a minimum 5 years with a Bachelor's and 3 years with a Master's)<br /> <br /> * Demonstrated experience with C#, C/C design, coding and testing<br /> <br /> * Demonstrated experience testing and troubleshooting software / hardware interfaces and applications<br /> <br /> * Demonstrated experience with Versioning Control software (i.e. GIT, TFS)<br /> <br /> Preferred Qualifications:<br /> <br /> * Technical certifications that support Software Development<br /> <br /> * Previous software development experience with ADA, FORTRAN, C/C and related software<br /> <br /> * Experience programming within the Window's Presentation Foundation (WPF)<br /> <br /> * Experience with automated testing and test systems<br /> <br /> * Experience with programming in the VAX/VMS hardware and software environment<br /> <br /> * Familiarity with software certification methodologies<br /> <br /> * Previous ICBM and or ALCS operations and software experience<br /> <br /> * Current active Top Secret security clearance<br /> <br /> * Requirements Analysis experience<br /> <br /> * Software Configuration Management<br /> <br /> * MS Windows Networking<br /> <br /> * Hardware architecture design<br /> <br /> Northrop Grumman is committed to hiring and retaining a diverse workforce. We are proud to be an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer, making decisions without regard to race, color, religion, creed, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, national origin, age, veteran status, disability, or any other protected class. For our complete EEO/AA and Pay Transparency statement, please visit www.northropgrumman.com/EEO. U.S. Citizenship is required for most positions.<p style='display: none; font-weight: bold;' hidden='hidden'>AC2019</p>]]></description><company><![CDATA[Northrop Grumman]]></company><postal_code>93437</postal_code><city>Vandenberg Air Force Base</city><state>CA</state><country>USA</country><url>https://www.startwire.com/jobs/vandenberg-afb-ca/software-engineer-543439114?source=appconnect-ua</url><posted_date>2019/05/12</posted_date><category>Engineering</category><ats>tee</ats><rpu_tag>medium</rpu_tag><employment_type>OTHER</employment_type><normalized_company>northrop-grumman</normalized_company><normalized_position>software engineer</normalized_position></job><job><job_reference>342450597</job_reference><position><![CDATA[Software Engineer]]></position><description><![CDATA[At Northrop Grumman we develop cutting-edge technology that preserves freedom and advances human discovery. Our pioneering and inventive spirit has enabled us to be at the forefront of many technological advancements in our nation's history - from the first flight across the Atlantic Ocean, to stealth bombers, to landing on the moon. We continue to innovate with developments from launching the first commercial flight to space, to discovering the early beginnings of the universe. Our employees are not only part of history, they're making history.<br /> <br /> No matter the assignment, Northrop Grumman is committed to being a leader in Cyber, Logistics and Modernization, Autonomous Systems, C4ISR, and Strike. For us, it's about more than just performing. It means realizing the values that define us: responsibility, trust, integrity and protecting freedom worldwide. These values inspire and unite our people- who make everything we do possible.<br /> <br /> The Engineering and Sciences (E&S) organization pushes the boundaries of innovation, redefines engineering capabilities, and drives advances in various sciences. Our team is chartered with providing the skills, innovative technologies to develop, design, produce and sustain optimized product lines across the sector while providing a decisive advantage to the warfighter. Come be a part of our mission!<br /> <br /> Northrop Grumman Mission Systems (NGMS) is looking for you to join our team as a Software Engineer based out of Aurora, CO.<br /> <br /> What You'll get to Do:<br /> <br /> * Serve as technical resource within the Software Department with some exposure to customer interface<br /> <br /> * Ability to work both independently and as part of a team with minimal supervision to prioritize tasks<br /> <br /> * Supporting, maintaining and documenting software applications<br /> <br /> * Developing software tools to complement maintenance activities<br /> <br /> * Ability to perform with a high level of attention to detail and minimal supervision<br /> <br /> * The integration and verification of new baselines with Postgres database.<br /> <br /> * Responsible for developing new software capabilities for operational users<br /> <br /> Additional Northrop Grumman Information:<br /> <br /> Northrop Grumman has approximately 85,000 employees in all 50 states and in more than 25 countries, we strive to attract and retain the best employees by providing an inclusive work environment wherein employees are receptive to diverse ideas, perspectives and talents to help solve our toughest customer challenges: to develop and maintain some of the most technically sophisticated products, programs and services in the world.<br /> <br /> Our Values. The women and men of Northrop Grumman Corporation are guided by Our Values. They describe our company as we want it to be. We want our decisions and actions to demonstrate these Values. We believe that putting Our Values into practice creates long-term benefits for shareholders, customers, employees, suppliers, and the communities we serve.<br /> <br /> Our Responsibility. At Northrop Grumman, we are committed to maintaining the highest of ethical standards, embracing diversity and inclusion, protecting the environment, and striving to be an ideal corporate citizen in the community and in the world.<br /> <br /> MSCOMSTR<br /> <br /> 1NGSPACE<br /> <br /> You'll Bring These Qualifications:<br /> <br /> * Bachelor's Degree within a STEM field (Science/Technical/Engineering/Math) from an accredited college with two (2) years of software engineering and development experience; zero (0) years of experience with Master's Degree<br /> <br /> * Active TS/SCI access (Top Secret, Sensitive Compartmented Information)<br /> <br /> * Willing to submit and obtain an adjudicated Counterintelligence (CI) Polygraph<br /> <br /> * Web development<br /> <br /> * Web developer<br /> <br /> These Qualifications Would be Nice to Have:<br /> <br /> * Adjudicated CI Polygraph (within 7 years)<br /> <br /> * Linux/Unix, PERL, GIT, and database experience<br /> <br /> * HTML/CSS, JavaScript<br /> <br /> What We Can Offer You:<br /> <br /> Northrop Grumman provides a comprehensive benefits package and a work environment that encourages your growth and supports the mutual success of our people and our company. Northrop Grumman benefits give you the flexibility and control to choose the benefits that make the most sense for you and your family. Your package will include the following:<br /> <br /> * Health Plan<br /> <br /> * Savings Plan<br /> <br /> * Paid Time Off<br /> <br /> * Additional benefits<br /> <br /> * Education Assistance<br /> <br /> * Training and Development<br /> <br /> * Wellness Program<br /> <br /> * Employee Discount Program<br /> <br /> * On-Site Fitness Center (available at some locations)<br /> <br /> https://benefits.northropgrumman.com/us/en2/BenefitsOverview/Pages/default.aspx<br /> <br /> Northrop Grumman is committed to hiring and retaining a diverse workforce. We are proud to be an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action Employer, making decisions without regard to race, color, religion, creed, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, marital status, national origin, age, veteran status, disability, or any other protected class. For our complete EEO/AA and Pay Transparency statement, please visit www.northropgrumman.com/EEO. U.S. Citizenship is required for most positions.<p style='display: none; font-weight: bold;' hidden='hidden'>AC2019</p>]]></description><company><![CDATA[Northrop Grumman]]></company><postal_code>80041</postal_code><city>Aurora</city><state>CO</state><country>USA</country><url>https://www.startwire.com/jobs/aurora-co/software-engineer-342450597?source=appconnect-ua</url><posted_date>2019/03/11</posted_date><category>Technology</category><ats>tee</ats><rpu_tag>medium</rpu_tag><employment_type>OTHER</employment_type><normalized_company>northrop-grumman</normalized_company><normalized_position>software engineer</normalized_position></job><job><job_reference>533239425</job_reference><position><![CDATA[Software Engineer]]></position><description><![CDATA[NJVC<br /> <br /> Company Job Title:<br /> <br /> Software Engineer<br /> <br /> Clearance:<br /> <br /> TS/SCI<br /> <br /> Location:<br /> <br /> Arnold, MO<br /> <br /> Reports To:<br /> <br /> Manager, Software Services<br /> <br /> FLSA Status:<br /> <br /> Exempt, Full Time, Regular<br /> <br /> Summary:<br /> <br /> The Software Engineer will provide sustainment and development for several systems.<br /> <br /> Duties and Responsibilities:<br /> <br /> * Design, modify, develop, write, and implement web applications.<br /> <br /> * Responsible for the continuation, integration, and follow-on enhancements to existing applications.<br /> <br /> * Produce application code with the following technologies - C#.NET MVC, Razor, Entity Framework Code First, NUnit, .NET Web API, CSS, Bootstrap, SOAP and REST Web Services, JSON, GIT<br /> <br /> * Manage data and data structures using MS SQL Server including understanding SQL and data modeling, data transformation objects and object relation mapping with Entity Framework<br /> <br /> * Create front end experiences with JavaScript (including libraries such as jQuery/Bootstrap) and other technologies such as HTML and CSS<br /> <br /> * Other duties as assigned<br /> <br /> Minimum Qualifications: (To perform this job successfully, an individual must be able to perform each essential duty satisfactorily.)<br /> <br /> * Master's Degree and 5 years of experience OR Bachelor's Degree with 7 years of experience or equivalent. Additional relevant experience may used in lieu of the degree requirement. Experience to include:<br /> <br /> * Experience with troubleshooting and correcting software bugs<br /> <br /> * Experience working with customers/product owners.<br /> <br /> * Experience working in a fast-paced environment with multiple changing priorities.<br /> <br /> * Previous development experience – web services, database applications, web application development<br /> <br /> * TS/SCI required<br /> <br /> Knowledge, Skills and Abilities:<br /> <br /> * Leadership and self-direction skills are highly desired.<br /> <br /> * Ability to solve complex engineering problems utilizing creative thinking skills.<br /> <br /> * Strong communication skills.<br /> <br /> * Knowledge of and ability to create REST endpoints<br /> <br /> * Ability to critically analyze and understand the systems and also communicate system requirements to the customer and leadership.<br /> <br /> * Familiarity with Agile development framework, preferably SAFe.<br /> <br /> * Ability to travel as required.<br /> <br /> * Ability to meet eligibility requirements of a government security clearance for access to classified information.<br /> <br /> Physical Demands: (The physical demands described here are representative of those that must be met by an employee to successfully perform the essential functions of this job. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.)<br /> <br /> * While performing the duties of this Job, the employee is regularly required to sit and talk or hear. The employee is frequently required to walk; use hands to finger, handle, or feel and reach with hands and arms. The employee is occasionally required to stand; climb or balance and stoop, kneel, crouch, or crawl. The employee must occasionally lift and/or move up to 25 pounds. Specific vision abilities required by this job include close vision.<br /> <br /> Work Environment: (The work environment characteristics described here are representative of those an employee encounters while performing the essential functions of this job.)<br /> <br /> * The employee will normally work in a temperature-controlled office environment, with frequent exposure to electronic office equipment.<br /> <br /> * During visits to areas of operations, may be exposed to extreme cold or hot weather conditions. Is occasionally exposed to fumes or airborne particles, toxic or caustic chemicals, and loud noise.<br /> <br /> Chenega Corporation and family of companies is an EOE.<br /> <br /> Equal Opportunity Employer/Veterans/Disabled<br /> <br /> Native preference under PL 93-638.<br /> <br /> We participate in the E-Verify Employment Verification Program.<br /> <br /> '445184<p style='display: none; font-weight: bold;' hidden='hidden'>AC2019</p>]]></description><company><![CDATA[NJVC]]></company><postal_code>63010</postal_code><city>Arnold</city><state>MO</state><country>USA</country><url>https://www.startwire.com/jobs/arnold-mo/software-engineer-533239425?source=appconnect-ua</url><posted_date>2019/05/02</posted_date><category>Engineering</category><ats>tee</ats><rpu_tag>medium</rpu_tag><employment_type>FULL_TIME</employment_type><normalized_company>njvc</normalized_company><normalized_position>software engineer</normalized_position></job></pmxi_records>