<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<pmxi_records><job><job_reference>309943909</job_reference><position><![CDATA[Software Engineer]]></position><description><![CDATA[Position Description<br /> <br /> Reporting to the Health Mart Atlas IT Director, this role will contribute to the design, architecture, and delivery of cutting-edge software to assist pharmacies in maximizing their reimbursements and providing transparency in payer contracting. This individual will be an instrumental role in the Health Mart Atlas development team and will provide critical input into product and feature design, tool selection, development processes, and the rearchitecting of legacy software.<br /> <br /> Key Responsibilities<br /> <br /> * Work closely with product owners, usability experts, and customers to develop and refine applications and features.<br /> <br /> * Staying up to date on latest technologies, open source projects and best practices.<br /> <br /> * Develop application code according to user stories, requirements, and acceptance criteria.<br /> <br /> * Promoting development best practices.<br /> <br /> * Maintaining and improving product security.<br /> <br /> * Ensuring compliance with HIPAA and other regulations.<br /> <br /> * Operations and production support.<br /> <br /> * Optimizing application performance and scalability.<br /> <br /> * Promoting standards-based healthcare interoperability with internal and external partners.<br /> <br /> Minimum Requirements<br /> <br /> * 4+ years experience in software development.<br /> <br /> Critical Skills<br /> <br /> * A DevOps mindset.<br /> <br /> * 2+ years of Java, Node.js, or Angular experience.<br /> <br /> * Agile development experience.<br /> <br /> * Test-Driven Development (TDD) or Behavior-Driven Development (BDD) skills.<br /> <br /> * Source code control with git.<br /> <br /> Additional Knowledge and Skills<br /> <br /> * Knowledge of EDI 835 standards.<br /> <br /> * Healthcare or pharmaceutical industry experience.<br /> <br /> * Strong object-oriented design.<br /> <br /> * Linux (RHEL) or Windows Server.<br /> <br /> * Cloud platform experience (Azure preferred).<br /> <br /> * NoSQL Database technologies.<br /> <br /> * C# .NET experience is a strong plus.<br /> <br /> * Serverless technologies.<br /> <br /> Education<br /> <br /> * 4-year degree in computer science or related field or equivalent experience. MS or BS in Computer Sciences or Engineering preferred.<br /> <br /> McKesson is an Equal Opportunity/Affirmative Action employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, creed, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, national origin, disability, or protected Veteran status.Qualified applicants will not be disqualified from consideration for employment based upon criminal history.McKesson is committed to being an Equal Employment Opportunity Employer and offers opportunities to all job seekers including job seekers with disabilities. If you need a reasonable accommodation to assist with your job search or application for employment, please contact us by sending an email to Disability_Accommodation@McKesson.com. Resumes or CVs submitted to this email box will not be accepted.Current employees must apply through internal career site.Join us at McKesson!<p style='display: none; font-weight: bold;' hidden='hidden'>AC2019</p>]]></description><company><![CDATA[McKesson Corporation]]></company><postal_code>75201</postal_code><city>Dallas</city><state>TX</state><country>USA</country><url>https://www.startwire.com/jobs/dallas-tx/software-engineer-309943909?source=appconnect-ua</url><posted_date>2019/03/05</posted_date><category>Technology</category><ats>workday</ats><rpu_tag>medium</rpu_tag><employment_type>OTHER</employment_type><normalized_company>mckesson-corporation</normalized_company><normalized_position>software engineer</normalized_position></job><job><job_reference>323868937</job_reference><position><![CDATA[Software Engineer]]></position><description><![CDATA[JobDescription :<br /> <br /> The Role: S&P Global Market Intelligence, a best-in-class sector-focused news and financial information provider, is looking for a Software Developer to join our Software Development team in either our Charlottesville office or our Richmond office.<br /> <br /> Location: Charlottesville, VA<br /> <br /> Please note: This position is limited to individuals who will not require company sponsorship now or in the future for continued employment.<br /> <br /> The Impact: You will utilize your technical knowledge and analytical skills to develop the products that our clients use daily. You will help provide mentorship and insight to other developers and stretch your knowledge as we come up with new solutions to the challenges we encounter. We provide the data and analytics required for every single day decisions in the capital and commodities markets.<br /> <br /> The Career Opportunity: Are you encouraged by meaningful tasks that can directly impact the business? Do you enjoy working with global teams? In this role, you have a tremendous opportunity to grow personally and professionally. As a software developer with us, the chance to work on enterprise level products and new technologies is presented constantly. Our technology is continuously evolving, ensuring that you are always learning new skills and facing new challenges. Your growth potential is endless.<br /> <br /> The Team / The Business: We have teams made up of people that learns how to work effectively together, while working with the larger group of developers on our platform. Opportunities are presented every single day to work with people from a wide variety of backgrounds and you have the opportunity to develop a close team dynamic with coworkers from around the globe.<br /> <br /> Job Responsibilities:<br /> <br /> * Solve problems, analyze and isolate issues<br /> <br /> * Provide technical guidance and mentoring to the team and help them embrace change as new processes are introduced<br /> <br /> * Champion practices and methodologies and serve as a SME to the organization<br /> <br /> * Build solutions to develop/support key business needs<br /> <br /> * Engineer components and common services based on standard development models, languages and tools<br /> <br /> * Produce system design documents and lead technical walkthroughs<br /> <br /> * Collaborate effectively with technical and non-technical partners<br /> <br /> * Continuously improve the architecture and quality of the code<br /> <br /> Experience and proficiency with a variety of System tools including:<br /> <br /> * Bachelor's /Master's Degree in Computer Science, Information Systems or equivalent.<br /> <br /> * Minimum of 1 year of experience in application development using Microsoft Technologies.<br /> <br /> * Knowledge of object-oriented design, .NET framework and design patterns.<br /> <br /> * Strong command of essential technologies: C#, SQL Server.<br /> <br /> * Proficient with software development lifecycle (SDLC) methodologies like Agile, Test- driven development.<br /> <br /> * Good experience with developing solutions involving relational database technologies on SQL Server platform, stored procedure programming experience using Transact SQL.<br /> <br /> Optional proficiency:<br /> <br /> * Big Data, Hadoop, SOLR, Spark, AWS<br /> <br /> About S&P Global Market Intelligence<br /> <br /> At S&P Global Market Intelligence, we know that not all information is important—some of it is vital. Accurate, deep and insightful. We integrate financial and industry data, research and news into tools that help track performance, generate alpha, identify investment ideas, understand competitive and industry dynamics, perform valuation and assess credit risk. Investment professionals, government agencies, corporations and universities globally can gain the intelligence essential to making business and financial decisions with conviction.<br /> <br /> S&P Global Market Intelligence is a division of S&P Global (NYSE: SPGI), which provides essential intelligence for individuals, companies and governments to make decisions with confidence. For more information, visit, S&P Global Market Intelligence<br /> <br /> To all recruitment agencies: S&P Global does not accept unsolicited agency resumes. Please do not forward such resumes to any S&P Global employee, office location or website. S&P Global will not be responsible for any fees related such resumes.<br /> <br /> S&P Global is an equal opportunity employer committed to making all employment decisions without regard to race/ethnicity, gender, pregnancy, gender identity or expression, color, creed, religion, national origin, age, disability, marital status (including domestic partnerships and civil unions), sexual orientation, military veteran status, unemployment status, or any other basis prohibited by federal, state or local law. Only electronic job submissions will be considered for employment.<br /> <br /> This program/position is limited to persons with indefinite right to work in the United States<br /> <br /> If you need an accommodation during the application process due to a disability, please send an email to:<p style='display: none; font-weight: bold;' hidden='hidden'>AC2019</p>]]></description><company><![CDATA[McGraw-Hill Financial]]></company><postal_code>22901</postal_code><city>Charlottesville</city><state>VA</state><country>USA</country><url>https://www.startwire.com/jobs/charlottesville-va/software-engineer-323868937?source=appconnect-ua</url><posted_date>2019/03/08</posted_date><category>Technology</category><ats>none</ats><rpu_tag>medium</rpu_tag><employment_type>OTHER</employment_type><normalized_company>mcgraw-hill-financial</normalized_company><normalized_position>software engineer</normalized_position></job></pmxi_records>